▍2026 辛辛那提 WTA1000 女双第一轮
科斯秋克/斯特恩斯 6-2 1-6 10-8 威廉姆斯姐妹 · 赛后新闻发布会
Hi Venus and Serena.
嗨 维纳斯 塞雷娜
I know it's not the result you wanted,
我知道这不是你们想要的结果
but I know this comeback together
但我知道这次搭档复出
in doubles was like four years in the making
打双打 你们等了差不多四年
and I know you wanted to play
我知道你们本来想
at Wimbledon, but to do it on home soil,
在温网打 换成了主场
just how special was it to finally, you know,
终于能够
reunite on the doubles court?
重聚双打场 这感觉多特别？
Yeah, I thought it was fun.
是啊 我觉得很好玩
I thought it was special.
我觉得很特别
I thought it was good.
感觉很好
We kicked off a little rust in the middle
我们中段打得有点生疏
of the match and just, you know,
就是
we're starting to feel it
慢慢找到感觉了
and it was it was really fun.
真的很好玩
It was it was really cool to to be able
能够
to do this again.
再打一次 真的很棒
Anything to add?
有什么想补充的吗？
I thought he asked Serena.
我以为他是问塞雷娜的
Okay.
好
Raise your hand just so they see you.
举下手 好让大家看到你
Having Serena.
呃 塞雷娜
Just Serena, I was just curious
就是想问塞雷娜 我很好奇
about how the Wimbledon experience
温网那段经历
was for you and what the knee injury,
对你来说是什么感觉 那个膝伤
what that was like, sustaining it,
受伤的那一刻是什么感觉
then recovering from it and and and
然后康复的过程
if if you left there wanting
你离开那儿的时候
to play more or if that was Yeah,
是还想接着打 还是
just how you kind of digested it as well.
你是怎么消化这件事的
That was a little traumatic experience
那对我来说
for me.
是一次有点创伤的经历
Took me like two hours
我花了差不多两个小时
to leave the locker room that night.
那天晚上才走出更衣室
And it's been a long recovery,
康复的过程很漫长
which is something I never thought
这是我从来没想过
I'd say cuz I never thought I'd
自己会说出的话
be here sitting talking to you all again.
又坐在这儿 跟大家聊天
But you know,
但是
what doesn't kill you make you stronger
杀不死你的都会让你更强大
and so it's good.
所以 挺好的
Next question.
下一个问题
Just raise your hand.
举手就行
What was going to make tonight a success
今晚要怎么样才算成功
when you take the result out of it?
抛开比赛结果不谈的话
What did you want to get out of this?
想从这场比赛得到什么？
You know, I think we always for us,
对我们来说
I think winning is obviously great,
赢球当然很棒
but I think in this position,
但站在这个位置上
just having, you know,
就是
fun like we're I didn't come out here
开心最重要 我们不是为了
to win this this tournament.
赢下这站比赛才来的
Obviously, I wanted to do the best
当然 我想尽自己所能
that I could do, but I think having fun
打到最好 但我觉得开心
and also just seeing how we are and
还有看看我们俩状态怎么样
how we feel out there and, you know,
在场上感觉如何
being out there with the fans, too,
还有跟球迷们在一起
is just really good just to give them another
这些都很好 也是再给他们
opportunity to see us play.
看我们打球的机会
You know, it was just really cool really.
真的挺棒的
And you're answering the next one.
下一个问题你来答
Okay, I'll pass back to
好 那我转给
It's going to be a little bit tricky
这个问题有点为难
because it was a question for Serena,
因为原本是塞雷娜的问题
but But obviously
不过
on a Monday night probably
周一晚上
the last few years you weren't
这几年你可能都没有
in the cauldron of competition,
站在这种竞技的漩涡中心
loud fans cheering you on or anything.
被震天响的球迷加油声包围
I'm curious, obviously you played on grass,
你之前打的是草地 我很好奇
you know, and had those leadups
有那些赛前热身
and had the experience,
也有过那种经历
but how is it jarring at all to kind
但回到
of get back into a raucous stadium
这么喧闹的球场 会不适应吗
or is it like riding a bike like, oh yeah,
还是说就像骑自行车一样
I this is exactly, you know, comfortable?
熟门熟路 完全不陌生？
I wouldn't say jarring,
我不会说不适应
but definitely I wouldn't say surprising,
但也说不上意外
but it's it's it's weird because I'm
但确实挺奇怪的 因为我
so not used to it.
已经很不习惯了
And I'm
我
so used to having a different night
已经很习惯周一晚上
on Monday night, but you know,
是完全不一样的安排
and Monday nights are, you know,
而现在周一晚上
I guess I never know what to expect.
我完全没法预料会是什么样
So,
所以
next question.
下一个问题
I'm thinking back to early days
我在回想早年
in Southern California,
在南加州的时候
two young girls hitting balls out
两个小女孩从购物篮里
of a shopping basket
掏球出来打
with their dad out on the court
跟爸爸一起在球场上
and I just wonder all these years later,
这么多年过去了 我很好奇
is the joy for the for the game the same
打球带来的乐趣
as it always was?
是不是还跟当年一样？
Or are you even enjoying yourself more out
还是说 现在打球
there?
反而更享受了？
I think the approach is definitely the same.
我觉得心态肯定是一样的
the process and the method.
过程和方法都一样
And I think that I take a lot of joy
我觉得自己从这个过程里
and perhaps Serena too in the process.
得到很多乐趣 塞雷娜大概也是
So I think we've been doing it
我们做这件事
so long too
已经太久了
and for Serena perhaps she was away
塞雷娜可能有过一段时间
and even I was away for a while too.
离开了 我自己也是
And it's like going back to ride a bike.
但这就像重新骑上自行车
It's like it's it's what you've always done.
这就是你一直在做的事
It's you almost expected of yourself.
几乎是你对自己的期待
I think there's joy.
我觉得里面还是有乐趣的
Why not?
为什么不呢
Yeah. I never really enjoyed the process,
嗯 我从没真正享受过这过程
but I think this time I'm enjoying
但我觉得这一次
the process a little bit more than I've ever
我更享受这个过程 比以往
have.
任何时候都多
And it's kind of just having a different view
而且现在看待它的角度
of it.
也不一样了
And it's also like this isn't forever.
而且这也不是一辈子的事
This is like not long.
不会持续太久
So, it's also just fun to to know that, too.
所以知道这一点 也挺开心的
And like I'm not playing every week,
我不是每周都在打比赛
you know, I'm not showing up every week.
不是每周都出现在场上
you have kids, so it's a little bit different.
而且有了孩子 情况不一样了
Okay, we'll do two more over there
好 那边再来两个问题
and then Yeah, that that's fine.
然后 嗯 可以
Sure.
没问题
For either of you,
问你们俩谁都行
when you're communicating in doubles,
打双打的时候你们沟通
is that something
这件事
that because you're sisters
是不是因为你们是姐妹
and because you've been together so long
又在一起这么久了
that that is that something that just kind
就自然而然
of picks up naturally from the start,
从一开始就能默契配合
even even though you've
哪怕
had a few years not playing together?
这几年没有一起打过球？
I think communication
我觉得沟通这件事
is something you can't take for granted
在任何事情上
in anything.
都不能想当然
No matter what, we have to communicate
不管怎样 我们都得沟通
just like any other team.
跟别的组合没什么两样
But I think that we give each other
但我觉得我们彼此
so much grace and encouragement
给了对方很多包容和鼓励
that maybe we I mean
我是说
this is our first time playing together
这是我们隔了这么久
in forever too
第一次一起打球
and I think we really were getting our stride
我们确实慢慢找到了节奏
for sure.
确实是
So this is this was great for us
所以这次对我们来说很棒
to like get out there and do it.
能站上场去打这一场
But communication is like always key
但沟通永远是关键
like every point you can't just be like read
每一分都不能指望
my mind being we have to still speak
对方能读懂心思 得开口说
to each other.
互相说清楚
Okay we'll do two more comments Dave
好 戴夫那边再来两个问题
and then to mine
然后轮到我这边
hometown tournaments are bit
主场作战这种事
of a rare thing in tennis
在网球里挺少见
so tonight Peyton Stearns
今晚斯特恩斯
is from Mason Ohio
就是俄亥俄州梅森人
and we talked to her and Marta downstairs
我们楼下采访了她和玛尔塔
for a few minutes and they talked
聊了几分钟 她们说
about how special this match was for them.
这场球对她们来说有多特别
Can you talk a little bit about Payton
能不能聊聊佩顿
and Marta and your thoughts on them?
还有玛尔塔 你们怎么看她们？
Well, I I don't know.
这个 我也说不好
I feel like Payton I to play
我觉得佩顿
in your hometown, she's from Mason.
能在自己家乡打球 她是梅森人
That's kind of awesome to be able to play
能在这么大一站比赛里打球
in such a big tournament that's literally
而且就在自己家门口
in your house.
这挺酷的
So that's that must be really special
这对她来说
for her.
肯定特别有意义
And I love that.
我很喜欢这一点
I love, you know,
我很喜欢
I love following all the American girls.
关注所有美国小将
I just really am big fans
我真的是她们的铁杆粉丝
and always supporting them.
一直支持她们
And and then Marta is I hit
还有玛尔塔 我在温网
with her at Wimbledon
跟她打过球
and she was just it was just different.
感觉很不一样
It was just so nice. She
特别好 她
was so it was really awesome
跟她打球
to hit with her and just to get
真的很棒 也借这个机会
to know her as much as I could while hitting
尽量多了解她
and and training together,
一起训练的时候
but it was still fun.
还是很开心
And yeah, I I really like, you know,
而且我特别喜欢
when she does back flips.
她做后空翻的样子
Okay, last one to
好 最后一个问题
finally I'm just curious which one
我很好奇 到底是谁
of you just decided to play doubles again?
先提议要重新打双打的？
What was that conversation like deciding
那次决定重返双打场
to get back on the doubles court?
对话是什么样的？
Um
呃
yeah, I I think we've waited a long time
我们等这一天
to get back on the doubles court even
已经等了很久了
this year.
就算是今年
Yeah.
嗯
So I think eventually we would find our way
所以我觉得我们迟早
to each other.
会重新走到一起
All right.
好
Thank you guys.
谢谢大家
Thank you.
谢谢